This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Initial
高举你的双手 [所有人都知道我无法停下]
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
把握住 崭新的明天 [不会停下]
(You don't stop)
迎风而立 看清自己 正是一直以来最大的梦想
It's a beautiful eternal dream...
...where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
让我们出发 让我们出发
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
哦 无人能阻止我们的崛起
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive go for the highest stake in the gamble.
行尸走肉地活着能成什么事
赌一把 心跳快得叫人紧张
同样的理想 同样地拼命
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
现在就来比比看谁的梦想更为炽热吧
You can never use the escalator.
没有电梯直达的不朽荣耀
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
让我们对锻炼身体说yeah
You must eventually climb the stairs.
反正早晚要爬上的阶梯
先在这里锤炼自己的内心好了
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
日渐颓废的每一天 [但你知道]
Intense days go by. (But you know?)
对值得攻下的关卡 也能一笑置之
Just laugh it off, 'cause it's a game worth competing.
让我们瞧瞧你的神速
Let's see how fast you can do it.
不要放下你举起的手 [所有人都知道我无法停下]
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
飞驰吧 无眠的挑战者 [不会停下]
(You don't stop)
寻找活在当下的理由
It's a quest of the never-ending dream...
...where you now search for the reason to live.
梦想无极限的征途
(Let's go)
让我们出发 让我们出发
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh, raise up your hands now.
哦 无人能阻止我们的崛起
２台の軸はずれていて
It's so hard to maintain control
because the two cars are misaligned.
バランスがとりにくい
It's an unrecoverable mistake.
とりかえしのつかないミスだったな
I can't get the maximum braking ability.
制動力をマックスに立ち上げられない
だめだ スピードが落ちてない
It's no good, we aren't slowing down.
止められない
I can't stop !
あんた一人に そこまでやらせるわけにはいかねえな
I'm not going to let you
do all of it by yourself.
感激したぜ
I'm so impressed ! Let me help !
手伝わせてくれ
Full Stop, And Beyond...
貴様ら
You guys...what are you...?
なにを
あっ これは 錯覚ではない
This...
...isn't my imagination.
いる 香織が来ている 香織か
She's here.
Kaori is here.
Kaori is...
香織がきていたんだ
Kaori was here.
感じなかったか 涼介
Did you sense it, Ryosuke ?
I did.
感じました 香織さんがいつもつけていた香水の匂いが
It was the scent of the
perfume she always wore.
あんな場所にあるはずのない匂いなのに
I shouldn't be able to
smell it in a place like this...
料金所の手前で 突然車に飛び込んできたんです
...but it suddenly entered
my car before the toll booth.
直感的に思いました 香織さんが来ているんだと
I intuitively realized Kaori was there.
先輩 俺たち二人は
Senpai, we must have
encountered some kind of miracle.
たぶんちょっとした奇跡に立ち会ったんだと思います
今日は彼女の命日なんですよ
Today's her anniversary.
It must be Kaori who saved you.
先輩を助けたのは 香織さんなんじゃないんですか
涼介 お前はばかじゃないのか
Ryosuke, are you stupid ?
明確な殺意を持って俺は後ろを走っていたんだ
I had solid hostile intent
as I drove behind you.
一つ間違えていれば おまえは殺人事件被害者なんだぞ
You would've been a murder
victim if the worst happened.
なのに なぜしれっとしていられる
How can you sound so nonchalant, as if it happened to someone else ?
他人事みたいに語っている場合かよ
何のことだか分かりませんね
I don't know what you're talking about.
We just had a "battle."
俺たちはバトルをしただけです
あなたが俺を本気で殺すつもりなら 簡単なことだ
It would've been easy to
kill me if you were serious...
でも そうはならなかった
...but it didn't turn out that way...
あなたが自分のルールを守っていたからだ
...because you followed your own rules.
That's why I accepted your challenge.
だから俺も受けて立った
持てる能力の全てを出し切って
We threw everything we had into it,
and now both of us are standing here.
俺たちは今 ここに立っている
最後の公道バトルの相手が あなただったことが
The fact that you were the opponent for my last
street battle means more than anything else to me.
何よりも価値があるんです
俺に 峠の楽しさを教えてくれたのは あなたですよ
It was you who taught me the
joy of driving the mountain pass.
先輩 あなたの前でいい走りができた
I was able to drive so well with you watching, so I'm satisfied from the bottom of my heart.
心から満足です
说得这么好听 其实是杀人未遂吧
俺にとっては それだけでいいんです
That's more than enough for me.
終わりにしよう
Let's put an end to this.
いくら考えても 答えは出なかった
I couldn't figure out why, no matter how hard I tried. It was just painful.
ただ苦しかった
I blamed myself every day, and spent a countless number of sleepless nights.
いつも自分を責めるだけで
眠れない夜が果てしなく続いた
ネガティブなイメージだけが膨らんでいくんだ
Only the negative images filled my mind.
But tonight, after racing with you, I feel like
something inside me was finally able to let go.
だけど 今夜 お前と走って
何かが吹っ切れた気がする
It was probably because I was able
to express my feelings to the fullest.
思いのたけを吐き出すことができたからだろう
お前は受け止めてくれた
And you responded.
どれほど言葉を連ねるよりも雄弁に伝わってくるものがあったよ
Your message was loud and clear,
and stronger than any words.
お前も俺と同じ苦しさを抱えている それがよく分かったんだ
I realized so well that you've
been suffering from the same pain.
すまなかったな 涼介 感謝している
I'm sorry, Ryosuke. Thank you for this.
無視しようと思えばそうすることもできたのに
You could have ignored me, but you came.
お前は来てくれた
お前と走りて満足だ
I'm satisfied having raced with you.
I can say that from the bottom of my heart.
心からそういえる
大事な車が擦り傷だらけですね
Your precious car is scratched up so badly.
すまんな やむにやまれぬ事情でね
Sorry, but it was unavoidable.
傷の一つ一つを見れば
I can imagine how difficult the situation
was just by examining those scratches.
どれほど苛酷な局面をくぐりぬけてきたのか 想像はつきますよ
あえて多くはいいません
I'm not going to say much.
I'm just glad you made it back safely.
よく無事で戻ってきました
さすがは高橋涼介 お疲れ様です
That's the Takahashi Ryosuke I know.
Well done.
俺自身も あの人と走ることによって
I feel like I was able to get
over a lot of things by racing him.
いろんなものが吐き出せた気がする
自分のためのバトルでもあったと思ってるよ
It was a battle for my own sake, too.
何かが違う
Something's changed.
涼介さんの表情が前と違う
Ryosuke's facial expression is different.
何かが吹っ切れたような いい表情になった
He looks better, as if he feels refreshed.
チームのリーダーとして
As a team leader who sends
two drivers into battle...
二人のドライバーを戦いに送り出す立場の俺は
最前線のリアルをどんな時も分かっていないといけない
...I must always know the reality of
what it's like to fight on the frontline.
その部分がぼやけることが一番こわい
What's most frightening is
becoming less sensitive to it.
But I was able to reassure myself
about my insight before the final battle.
最終戦を前にそこをきっちりと確認することができたよ
神奈川エリアでもっともリスキーなステージで
I've done everything I could for
the riskiest stage in Kanagawa.
やれるだけのことはやった
内のダブルエースはもう俺を超えている
Our double-aces have already surpassed me.
They should be fine.
あの二人なら大丈夫だ
後一戦です 勝ちに行きましょう 全力で
One more battle to go.
Let's do our best to win.
いよいよあと一週間か プロジェクトD の神奈川最終戦
One week until Project D's
final battle in Kanagawa.
サイドワインダーのダウンヒルはどんなドライバーかな
I wonder what sort of driver
Sidewinder's downhiller is.
車種とかも気になるんな
I'm also curious about what
kind of car he's going to drive.
まぁ どんなやつが出てこようが
Well, whoever he is,
he'll be no match for Takumi.
拓海に死角はないですけどね
そう思うんだけどさ
That's what I think, too.
神奈川遠征が始まったばかりのころ
But remember Kenji mumbling about something just when the Kanagawa battles started ?
健二がぼふっといってたことがあるよな
そのコースだけに めちゃめちゃ特化したスペシャリストがいたら
I'm afraid of a driver who's
specialized in a particular course.
やっぱりこわいな
それこそ秋名で連戦連勝してた拓海みたいなイメージの走り屋がさ
The kind of driver like Takumi
who won race after race on Akina.
いないですって そんなの
That's impossible.
拓海は特別ですよ
Takumi's one of a kind, because he didn't grow up in an ordinary family.
家庭環境が普通じゃないですから
親がよっぽと変わりもんじゃないと
Parents have to be
eccentric for that to happen.
あれはないでしょう
そこりゃ
Well that's...
特別な環境と特別な才能がはぐくんだ
He's a natural racer with a
special environment and talent.
neta:乾信司即拓海最终战对手被称为另一个天然(natural)
天然のドライバーですよ
You honestly think there's another
strange family like them in Kanagawa ?
あんな変な親子は神奈川にいるかって話です
まあな
Probably not.
其实这台车已经不是86了…
きたきた  ちょっとうるさい車
Here comes that "slightly loud" car.
美佳 制服か
You're still wearing your uniform, Mika ?
そうだよ だって 帰って着替える時間なかっただもん
Yep. I didn't have time
to go home and change.
珍しくないでしょう
It's not that uncommon, right ?
自分だって去年まで制服着てたくせに
I mean, up until last year
you were wearing one, too.
似合う 美佳のセーラー服
Do I look good in the sailor-style uniform ?
自分の彼女が女子高生だって 実感したでしょう
You came to realize your girlfriend is a high school girl, didn't you ?
それはまぁ
Well yeah, but you won't be
able to play golf that way.
けど それだと
今日は ゴルフは無理だろう
平気だよ 美佳は今日コーチだから
No worries, because I'm your coach today.
また右か
To the right again.
どうしても右だな
It goes to the right no matter what I do.
曲がるけど よくなったね拓海君
It does curve, but you've improved, Takumi.
初めてのころとは別人だよ
You're totally different from the first time.
やっぱり男の子って痩せってても力あるんだよね
Even a skinny guy has some muscle, after all.
まあね
Maybe. I think my arms are strong
because of the Eight-Six's steering.
俺結構腕力がある子だと思うよ
86のステアリングで鍛えられているから
祖都是方向盘强度设到10的
めっちゃ重いんだ あれ
It's so heavy.
打つときに右手が強いから曲がるんだけどね
It curves like that because you put
too much strength in your right arm.
ちょっと貸してみて
Let me use your club for a sec.
When the club is in this position,
the face should look like this.
クラブがこの位置の時は フェースはこうかな
よく分かんないな
I don't really understand.
Can you show me how ?
美佳 やって見て
じゃ 後ろから見てて
Well then, watch me from behind.
Like this...
こうだよ
...and just lift the club naturally...
あとはそのまま 持ち上げるだけ
美佳 かわる
Mika...
...I'll do it.
打っちゃだめ
You shouldn't.
池谷 イツキ
Iketani, Itsuki !
どうした 健二
What's the matter, Kenji ? You look upset.
血相を変えて ばあちゃんがまた行方不明か
Did your grandma go missing again ?
返事でもねえこというな
Don't go and jinx us like that.
週末の箱根の最新情報だよ
I've got the latest info on
this weekend's race in Hakone.
相変わらず秘密主義で
They're so secretive, that I don't know much in detail, except for one thing.
詳しいことは何も分からないんだけど 一つだけ
サイドワインダーのダウンヒル担当ドライバーについての情報が
We didn't know anything about
Sidewinder's downhill driver, right ?
今までなかったじゃん
何か 分かったのか
What do you know about him ?
それがさドライバーのことはまだ何も分からないんだけど
Actually, I don't know anything
about the driver himself...
...but apparently, his car is an Eight-Six.
車が86らしいんだよ
はっ 86
An Eight-Six ?
その86って トレノなんですか レビンなんですか
Is it a Trueno or Levin ?
そこまではまだわからないよ
I don't know that much yet.
しかも そこは重要なとこじゃないだろう
Besides, that's not important, is it ?
それは まぁ 確かに
You're absolutely correct.
86対86か
Eight-Six versus Eight-Six, huh ?
ラッキーで考えるべきでしょう
It's fortunate because Takumi won't lose, if both cars are Eight-Sixes.
同じ86なら 拓海が負けるわけないって言うか
There shouldn't be any other Eight-Six drivers who are better than Takumi.
拓海よりうまい奴なんているわけないですって
I was nervous, not knowing what the
opponent's car was, but now I feel relieved.
どんな車種か分からないうちは不安ですだけど
これでもう安心ですよ
テクニック勝負に持ち込めれば 絶対拓海のもんですよ
Once Takumi engages in a fight of
driving technique, he'll win for sure.
単純にそう考えるのはあまいぞ イツキ
It's too naive to simplify
the matter like that, Itsuki.
俺も同感だな めちゃめちゃいやな感じだよ
I feel the same way.
I've a bad feeling because it's so ominous...
不気味で仕方ない
神奈川最強といわれるサイドワインダーが
...for Sidewinder, which is the best in Kanagawa, to use an Eight-Six.
わざわざ86をぶつけてくるなんて
どれだけ自信持ってるかって話だよ
It's a matter of confidence.
相手方にも物凄く切れる参謀がいるらしいからな
They appear to have a very good strategist.
I don't think he staged a battle between two
Eight-Sixes just to make the show more interesting.
ただ盛り上がるためだけに
86対決を演出してきたわけじゃないだろうし
プロジェクトDを迎え打つために 万全の準備をしてるはずなんだ
They must be doing
everything to counter Project D.
拓海の快進撃を止めるために
Their choice of an Eight-Six as their final weapon to stop Takumi's consecutive wins may be a sign of confidence.
自信を持って送り出してくる 最終兵器が86だってことじゃないのか
こうしてみている分には
He drives so smoothly that he doesn't leave any strong impression at all.
スムーズのだけでこれといったインパクトはないんですわね
それでもタイムを計れば
But if you time him, he drives this downhill
faster than any of the Sidewinder members.
サイドワインダーのどのクルマよりも速く下ってしまう
おまけにこのコース以外は走られへんときいてる
Plus, he doesn't drive any other course.
This world is full of strange talents.
世の中には奇妙な素材がおろもんやな
あんな子供がなぜこれほどの芸当を身につけたんか
I wonder how a kid like
him acquired such skill.
不思議でならんわ
It's perplexing.
常識とされているドラテクのセオリーとは
It's something beyond the common notion of what driving technique should be.
別のところに存在する なにかや
Even Project D will be caught off guard.
さすがのプロジェクトDもドぎも抜かれるで
あいつが R32を処分したらしい
He got rid of his R32.
あいつって凛さんのことか
Do you mean Rin ?
そうさ
Yes.
何がきっかけであいつが変わったのかはわからないがな
I don't know what made him change.
死神GTRが箱根に出没することはもう二度とない
The Grim Reaper GT-R will
never appear in Hakone again.
どういう風のふきまわしか
I don't know what happened to him...
以前の職場に復職ねがいが出されているそうだ
...but I've heard that he's requested
to return his former position at work.
北条家にとってはいいことじゃないのか
It's good for the Hojo family, isn't it ?
そうかもしれないが
Probably so, but it
doesn't mean anything to me.
俺にとっちゃどうでもいい
Little kids maybe, but we're not at the age where we can
just up and go back to being friendly siblings just like that.
ガキならともかく
今さら兄弟仲良くって年でもないしな
いい年して
It's creepy for brothers
our age to be so clingy.
アニキアニキってのもきもいだろうが
何がプロジェクトDだ
Project D, my ass.
I'll defeat you, Takahashi Keisuke.
俺が止めらせ 高橋啓介
どうですか 新しいセットアップは
How is the new setup ?
赤城道路だといい感じだけど
It feels good on Akagi's roads...
箱根に乗り込んでデータを採ってみないと
...but I can't say much until
we get some data in Hakone.
なんともいえないな
早いとこ最終ステージのコースを攻めたいぜ
I want to tackle the final stage real soon.
イメージトレーニングはもうやりあきてるんだ
I'm tired of image training.
箱根遠征の間 カレンダーにまるつけておくから
I'll circle the dates of my Hakone
expeditionary race on the calendar...
配達の日付間違えんなよ
...so don't forget your
delivery dates, okay ?
おいよ
Got it.
すげえもんだな
His tire management is impressive...
このタイヤの使い方
けどひっかかるな
But something bothers me...
コントロールできすぎなとこが
The control is too perfect.
啓介 藤原 きてくれ
Keisuke, Fujiwara, come over here.
分かってると思うけど 今回のコースは長い
As you know, this course is long, so it's physically impossible to practice on everything in one day.
一日のプラクティスですべてをつめていくのは物理的に無理だ
So cut it to the bare minimum.
だから思い切って絞り込め
勝負どころだと感じるポイントを走りながら自分で見つけて
Find what will become the key to victory as
you drive, then expand your scope from there.
そこから広げていくんだ
全部やろうと思えば中途半端なものになる
If you try to do everything,
it'll only be half finished.
明日のドッグファイトをイメージしながら
Imagine tomorrow's dogfight, and take a practical
strategy of knowing what to focus on and what not to.
メリハリをつけて
実戦的な攻撃で行こう
お前たちにはそれができるはずだ
I'm sure both of you can do that.
よし いけ
Then go.
コース長いからな
The course is so long that it'll take longer than usual to complete their routine.
ルーティンをこなすだけで いつもより時間がかかるだろう
日の出まではみっちり走りこませるから
I'm going to let them practice
thoroughly until dawn, so be prepared.
たのむぞ
分かった
Got it.
I'll get more food
than usual for tonight.
いつもより多めに 夜食の買出しをしておくよ
腹がへっちゃ 戦はできないしな
They say you can't fight
on an empty stomach.
Thanks, Fumihiro.
I'm counting on you.
すまんな 史浩
頼りにしてるぜ
あのさ 松本
Hey, Matsumoto, you
know something, don't you ?
おまえ何か知ってるんじゃないのか
なにをですか
About what ?
涼介のことに決まってるだろう
About Ryosuke, of course.
He's acting differently.
何か雰囲気が違うんだよな
そりゃ まぁ 最終戦ですからね
Well, it must be because
this is the final battle.
I'm sure he's focused.
集中してると思いますよ
いや そういうんじゃないんだよ
No, that's not what I mean.
何か吹っ切れた感じっていうのか
It's like he's relaxed,
like he's smiling more often.
前よりも笑うっていうか
なぁ 松本
Matsumoto, if you know something, tell me.
知っているなら教えてくれよ
さぁ 何も知らないですよ
Well...
...I don't know anything, really.
自分で聞いてみたらどうです 直接本人に
Why don't you ask him yourself ?
どう思う 久保さん
What do you think, Kubo ?
向こうのFD 前回のスパイラル戦の時とイメージが違うな
That FD is giving off a different feeling from the last battle against Spiral.
今回の決戦に向けて かなりいじってきたのかもしれないぜ
It might have been
modified a lot for this battle.
どうですかな
I don't know.
カーボンのフードに換えてきたんで
The outer appearance is different
because of the carbon fiber hood...
見た目のイメージは変わりましたが
...but the insides shouldn't have changed much.
中身はそう大きくは換えんでしょう
気になるぜ
I'm worried. Forget about the Eight-Six.
86はいい
FDのデータを集中的に集めるように指示してくれ
Instruct everyone to focus
their data collection on the FD.
やれと言われればやりますが
If you say so, I'll do it...
本間に86はいいんですか
...but are you sure about the Eight-Six ?
シンジの走りにデータは無意味だ
Data is meaningless for Shinji's driving.
あってもそれを生かせないし なくても必ず勝つだろう
He won't be able to make use of the data.
Even if he doesn't have it, he'll still win.
シンジはそういうドライバーだ ちがうか 久保さん
Shinji is that kind of driver.
Don't you think so too, Kubo ?
ちがわんでしょうな
You're right.
FDを集中的にたのむ
Focus on the FD.
Obtain as much information on its section times
to determine how its fighting potential varies.
区間タイムをなるべく多く集めて
戦闘力の変化をきっちり見極めてくれ
わかりました 手配しましょう
Alright, I'll arrange that.
やれやれ
Oh man, our boss is nervous.
ナーバスになっとる うちの大将は
相手方の陽動作戦に見事にのせられとるがな
He fell for our opponent's diversion strategy.
ここまで来て大きくスペックを変えるわけがない
They shouldn't have changed the
specs very drastically at this point.
あのFDはもう完成してバランスがとれている
That FD is a completely balanced machine.
俺はだまされんぞ 高橋涼介
I won't be tricked, Takahashi Ryosuke.
あんたとの知恵くらべや相手にとって不足はない
This is our match of intelligence.
You're worthy of being my opponent.
よ ゼロの兄さん
Hey, Mister Zero.
Well, if it isn't the hot-blooded 246 guy.
誰かと思えば
246の熱血アニキじゃないか
いよいよ来るところまできたって感じだな
It has finally come to the
moment of truth, hasn't it ?
俺の予想では
I was expecting you to stop them.
あんたのところで止めてくれると思ってたんだけどな
すまんな 力不足で
Sorry that we weren't good enough.
高橋啓介 どんなドライバーだ
Takahashi Keisuke...
How do you rate him ?
ハーフウエットでのアクセルコントロールが抜群にうまかったな
His accelerator technique on
a half-wet road was exceptional.
He managed to control the traction of the
rear tires, as if they were a part of his body.
リアタイヤに体の神経が同調しているかのような
トラクションのコントロールができていた
勝負どころでの集中力というか きりかえもすごい
Besides his concentration right at the moment of attack,
his ability to switch mindsets quickly is also impressive.
ブースターに点火したジェット戦闘機のような
He reaches beyond the scope of Zero Theory, like a fighter jet boosted by an afterburner.
ゼロ理論ではありえない領域に入っていく
つまりあんたに似たタイプかな
In other words, he's like you.
俺に
Like me ?
闘争心をむき出しにして乗っていくタイプだ
The type of driver who shows his eagerness for
victory, who has skills and understands the theory.
技術もあるし理屈もわかっているが
最後は気持ちで行く感覚派だろう
But in the end, what
matters most is the spirit.
あんたと高橋啓介はそういうところが似ている
You and Takahashi Keisuke
are alike on that account.
ふうん 悪い気はしないがね
I don't feel bad hearing that.
What kind of driver is Fujiwara Takumi ?
藤原拓海は どんなドライバーだい
あんたに聞いておきたいね
I want to hear your opinion since you witnessed his true potential.
一番リアルなところを見てきているわけだからな
あいつは表現するのがむずかしいな
It's difficult to describe him.
It's like a black hole.
まるでブラックホールとでもいうか
Black hole ?
ブラックホール
なんでも貪欲にほうりこんでいくスペースの広さがある
He has a wide margin to be able to absorb a lot.
かたくななまでに自分のスタイルがあるようでいて
He appears to have his own concrete policy, but in
reality, he has no color. He's transparent and flexible.
本当は無色透明で柔軟だ
一戦ごとに確実に成長しているはずだ
He improves race after race, so he's probably different from when he raced against me.
たぶん俺が戦った時のあいつと今のあいつは
もう同じじゃない
高い評価だな
So you think highly of him,
almost raving about him.
絶賛じゃないか
それならばプロジェクトＤ対サイドワインダー
Then what's your prediction for this
battle between Project D and Sidewinder ?
この対決 どううらなう
ザックリと来たな
You want to cut to
the point, don't you ?
残念ではあるけど
It's unfortunate...
サイドワインダーが勝つだろうね
...but Sidewinder will win.
俺も同じ答えだ
I've come to the same answer.
I really admire Takahashi Ryosuke.
俺は高橋涼介という男にホレこんでいてね
神奈川エリアの一員としては大きな声では言えないが
As a member of a Kanagawa area team, I can't openly say this, but my emotional side wants Project D to win.
心情的にはプロジェクトＤに勝たせたいと思う
だが無理だ
But that's impossible.
サイドワインダーには十分な時間があった
Sidewinder had plenty of time to prepare.
久保英次という参謀がついているかぎり
As long as they have Kubo Eiji as their
strategist, they don't have any weaknesses.
死角はない
だけど 勝負はやってみなければわからない
But you can't really tell
until they start racing.
プロジェクトＤが勝つ可能性がないわけではない
It's not like Project D
has no chance of winning.
ドライバーの成長がわずかな希望だ
They have a slight chance due
to their drivers' improvements.
勝てる確率は 五分の一ってとこか
I say their chance of winning
is one-fifth, which is 20%.
20パーセント程度の勝算ということだ
なんか偉いことになってるぜ
This is getting ridiculous.
I've never seen so many
guys with stopwatches before.
今までと比べものにならないくらいの人数が
ストップウォッチもって立ってる
Don't they have anything else to do ?
どんだけ暇なのって話だよ
それをいうなら
Speaking of which, we aren't that different, coming all the way from Gunma only to race in Hakone.
わざわざ群馬から箱根まで峠攻めに来る俺たちも同じだろう
それもそうだけどさ
Well, that's true.
区間タイム計られてるぜ
They're measuring my
section times pretty closely.
かなり細かく区切ってやってる感じ
それもちょっとイヤだな
I don't like them trying
to figure out our strategy.
こっちの手の内をさぐられるのは
カムフラージュのパターンを１枚ふやそうか
Should I add another camouflage pattern ?
それはしない いつもと同じだ
No, don't.
Just do as normal.
ヘタに動いて
I'm afraid that you won't finish
practice if you try to do it differently.
プラクティスが不十分な終わり方をすることの方がこわい
ここまで来れば
At this point, we don't
have to modify our style.
ふだんどおりの俺達のスタイルはくずさない
わかったよ
I got it.
せいぜいおがませてやるよ
I'll let them watch and learn the style of
Project D, the best of the northern Kanto area.
北関東最強のプロジェクトＤのスタイルを
まぁ そういう意味だ
Yup, that's exactly what I meant.
どうしますか
What should I do then ?
足回りはCパターンだ
Set the suspension to pattern C,
and add 10 liters of gas.
ガソリンも10リッター足してくれ
気がついたか 藤原
Did you notice a huge number
of scouts throughout the course ?
コースのあちこちに偵察舞台がすごいんだって
Keisuke told me about them,
and tons of stopwatches, too.
啓介が言っていたんだ
すごい数のストップウォッチだってさ ほら
Here you go.
ああ 確かに人はたくさんいるけど
There're quite a lot of people out there, but they aren't pushing the buttons.
押してないですよ ボタン
１戦目から タイム計ってメモとかしてる人達いたんですよ
I noticed those who were keeping
time and taking notes from the first round.
たぶん同じ人達だと思います
I'm sure they're the same people. I remember some of their faces.
見おぼえある顔いましたから
でも今日はボタン押してないですね
But today none of them pressed
the button on their stopwatches.
確かか 藤原
Are you sure, Fujiwara ?
Yes.
はい
走りながら そんなとこまで気がついてる
He noticed such small
details while he was driving...
こいつが すごい
That's what makes him so great.
でもどういうことかな涼介
But what's the meaning of this, Ryosuke ?
It contradicts what Keisuke said.
啓介の話とちがってるのは
いいんだ
That's fine. Both of
them are telling the truth.
２人が言っていることはそれぞれ正しい
想定どおりさ
It's going as planned.
And so, the day of the final battle in Kanagawa has arrived...
Fujiwara Takumi:
Takahashi Ryosuke:
Hojo Rin:
Takahashi Keisuke:
Hojo Gou:
Kubo:
Miki Shinichiro
Koyasu Takehito
Nakamura Yuichi
Seki Tomokazu
Kiuchi Hidenobu
Kase Yasuyuki
日の暮れに 変わらない景色
Even when night falls, the scenery remains unchanged.
Takeuchi Itsuki:
Iketani Koichiro:
Kenji:
Uehara Mika:
Ikeda Ryuji:
Omiya Satoshi:
Matsumoto:
Fumihiro:
Mechanic:
Bunta:
Iwata Mitsuo
Yao Kazuki
Takagi Wataru
Hayami Saori
Nakai Kazuya
Touchi Hiroki
Nishi Rintaro
Hosoi Hajime
Takahashi Ryokichi
Ishikuza Unsho
振り返る 辿ってきた道
Looking back at the path I've taken.
切なさも 喜びも 消えない痛みも
Sadness, happiness, incurable pains...
Realizing that there are too many to count, as I walk alone.
数えてたら限がないねと独り歩く
A
Central Anime
Production
Translation:
Hiro-kun
Timing:
Todd Perkins
Editing:
Lillian-Hime
Barbara
Todd Perkins
Brain
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Nomake
Countless number of memorable scenes.
数え切れないほどの残像 ギャンブル生き抜いてきた残党
We lived through the hustle and bustle.
時に戦い 時に解りあい きれい事ばかりじゃなかった真実
Sometimes we argued, sometimes we understood.
It wasn't always pretty, but I keep the truth to myself...
背負ったまま新たな一歩
...as I take a new step.
あかね雲が街を染める この行く先をそっと問いかけて見る
Rosy clouds embellish the city.
I quietly ask about my future.
空はなにもいわず だけど私にこの道を照らしている
The sky remains silent.
Only illuminating this path before me.
透き通る景色を感じて
Feel the translucent scenery.
旋律を夕陽が奏で
The setting sun plays a melody.
透き通る景色を感じて
Feel the translucent scenery.
The setting sun plays a melody.
旋律を夕陽が奏で